How long have you been here?
For about an hour.
But shouldn't you be asking
why I came here in the first place?
You knew, didn't you?
Ever since that day.
Why am I...
What on earth is happening?
I must go to the palace.
Is that...
a Baekjeong mask?
Black clothes.
Physician's robe.
Actually, Eun-jo must have seen him
better than me.
Physician Hong was there too?
How did you know
I was at the constabulary?
Well...
In any case,
I'm so glad that you solved this case.
How fortunate.
It was you.
Gil-dong.
Where's Gil-dong?
He's not here.
Let's go that way.
He might have gone this way.
Come on.
Gil-dong would've gotten away just fine.
That would be a relief.
- Is that Eun-jo?
- What?
Hello, my body...
- Eun-jo!
- Oh, dear!
- Eun-jo! Oh, dear.
- Eun-jo!
Why didn't you ask me sooner?
Because you would've tried to hide it.
That night,
I heard from the soldiers
why they were chasing Gil-dong.
Gil-dong's name was written in blood,
but you couldn't have murdered
the Chief Censor
during your own wedding.
And
even if it was you,
you would've hidden it anyway.
But seeing that you're here,
it couldn't have been you.
It seems like
we're here for the same reason.
We're both here to see
if someone would come collect
the fake Gil-dong's body.
I'm sorry
I've been lying to you.
No need to apologize.
For a woman to step forward
and offer help to those people,
that's something that deserves praise.
So don't make a face like that.
It's my face.
He's buried over there.
I just want to pay my last respects.
Who's there?
What's going on?
What's happening?
It is a wild animal?
Lady Dong-ju, don't worry!
You're the one acting wild.
Are you trying your luck with me?
Do you know why he stopped there?
Wild animals, like tigers, roam that path.
That person framed you for murder.
I must know who this person is.
Let's stop chasing. It's too dangerous.
I don't care.
I care.
I don't want you to get hurt
because of this.
In case you forgot,
you're in my body.
What if you go
and get mauled by an animal?
It's my body.
Right.
I forgot.
Do you have anyone in mind
who might have killed the Chief Censor?
That man was hated by half the capital.
That means half the capital
would have wished him dead.
It might be difficult
to catch the culprit now.
After tonight, they will stay in hiding.
Why did they show up
at the constabulary as Gil-dong?
They wanted to stage Gil-dong's death
and bring the case to an end.
They needed a suspect
the people would believe,
and that was Gil-dong.
People would think
Gil-dong was really dead.
For a mere petty thief,
he gained far too much fame
and stirred up too many rumors.
I don't mean to dishonor the dead,
but perhaps it's best
that Gil-dong is forgotten like this.
Wait.
Are you saying
you will keep stealing?
Your silence says yes.
I just can't say
that I won't.
The reason I pretended
not to know you were Gil-dong
was because you wouldn't be able to steal
while our bodies were switched.
And I won't, so don't worry.
Do you think I'm worried about myself?
As I said, for a woman to step forward
and help those in need is admirable.
But I can only say that
because it already happened.
Things are different now.
That woman is you.
The theft, the fall,
being framed for murder,
all that dishonor falls upon you now.
Do you know how I felt on my way
to see the fake Gil-dong's body?
I blamed myself, and hated myself
for hiding you and not stopping you,
thinking I had brought you to that end.
You don't need to think that way.
I was never caught and--
You were already caught,
by me.
I'm warning you,
it doesn't matter whose body you're in.
If you ever steal again,
you will get caught again.
And just like last time,
it'll be by me.
Once again, he caught me.
I'll get going.
Halt.
What's that woman doing here at this hour?
A man?
Unbelievable.
INSTRUCTIONS FOR WOMEN
My lady!
The lord is arriving soon.
Hurry!
Oh, on my way.
My lady.
You have returned, Brother.
I told you to see to your appearance,
even for a brief outing.
- Pardon?
- My lady.
Your shoes.
I was so excited to see you.
Don't put this on me.
Here.
Take this to your fiancé.
The funeral must have worn him out.
About my marriage--
Your wedding will be postponed.
Holding two major family affairs
in the same year would be
too great a burden for his family.
You don't look like him.
You're beautiful.
My lady.
Did you laugh?
No, it's because I don't look like you...
No.
I mean...
What I meant was...
My lady!
You don't look like him.
You're beautiful.
Why did it come to mind at that moment?
Am I really that beautiful?
Or was it an exclamation?
Just like saying mountains are high
and flowers are pretty?
How long have you been standing there?
Since you started talking to yourself.
So you heard everything.
Here.
It's from my older brother.
He still thinks you're my fiancé.
I will bring up
our broken engagement today.
As you please.
You still seem to be in low spirits.
The fight for survival
that you mentioned on the rainy day
must still be ongoing.
Most definitely not.
If you'll excuse me.
That can't be true.
Oh, my.
Dressed like that, you really
do look like a lady of the annex.
How do I tie this?
I'm in no mood to see anyone.
Who is looking for me?
The Chief Secretary's eldest son?
Why did you want to meet me,
Young Master?
Were you with a man last night?
A man?
Did he see her with me last night?
I don't understand
what you're talking about,
Young Master.
Look at that shameless face of yours,
just like your father's.
What is all this noise about?
Father,
I saw this woman with a man last night.
Is that true?
Even the Chief Secretary...
Wait.
The Chief Secretary's eldest son
comes to the palace every day.
There is no way he didn't recognize me.
Must I even answer such a vulgar question?
What did you just say?
A truly virtuous man
asks for the full circumstances first,
even if he has his doubts.
The man I met yesterday
was the young master of my natal family.
Who did you think he was?
Did you not see his face?
I didn't get a look at it.
But the mere fact that a girl was out
at such a late hour...
A girl?
I may not be of a high status,
but I'm your senior by family order.
Choose your words carefully.
Above all, to dishonor me
is to dishonor your late grandfather,
which is something
a scholar-official must know.
Even when the royal family
takes in a concubine of low status,
she's granted a rank befitting
her position and treated with due respect.
And look at your attitude.
What? Have you forgotten your place?
Watch your words.
Father.
He's not wrong.
Observe proper decorum.
The devotion you should have shown
in serving my father
shall now be devoted
to honoring him for the rest of your life.
Seung-jae, follow me
once you're ready to go to the palace.
Yes, Father.
I'll see you later.
If I must.
Lay a finger on this body,
and you'll be beheaded at once.
What is it?
I thought I would have a word
with my grandchild.
The men of this family
seem to have never learned
how to treat their elders,
so I was teaching them.
Mark my words,
from now on,
you'd better not say things like,
"a mere lowly girl,"
"a mere concubine,"
or anything about ruining or killing me.
If you say any of those things,
you'll be in serious trouble.
I was going to ruin you completely,
but it no longer seems worth it.
What?
I get it.
This is why you lied
about who you were marrying.
You must've been counting days.
Be honest with me.
You just wanted a higher status.
Yes, apparently.
It turns out that
you were not a filial daughter
who cared for her family,
but someone who only wanted
the title, wealth and higher status
that came
with the Chief Secretary's family.
It's so typical.
It's boring.
Look, Grandchild,
I wasn't speaking of status,
but of basic respect for human beings.
Was it too hard for you to understand?
Well,
I'm not interested
in your worldly way of thinking,
much less in lecturing you.
So let's just stick to basic courtesy.
You are no different from others.
Why don't you show that man
this side of yourself?
It would make a much stronger impression.
"That man"?
What?
There's another man?
Deliver this to Her Majesty.
And convey my regards.
Her Majesty has ordered that
Your Highness pay his respects
in person today.
You should eat jujubes,
instead of sweet snacks like yakgwa.
Your Majesty has a cold constitution,
so it's good for your body.
Open wide.
I hear you go to the Royal Pharmacy
every morning to have the tonic prepared.
Yes, Your Majesty.
What wicked scheme are you plotting?
I want to clear up that misunderstanding.
Misunderstanding?
Your son...
I mean, me.
I am not the scoundrel
or idler you think I am.
I mean, I know I'm mischievous,
arrogant at times, stubborn,
occasionally act entitled, and...
Well, I'm a prince,
so I guess I am privileged.
Anyway,
I know how to give to those in need,
and at times show great generosity.
I can accept rejection with grace,
and even wish them happiness.
I can hide others' weaknesses and--
You have a knack for praising yourself.
Praising myself is, after all,
praising Your Majesty.
And this is
all thanks to Your Majesty's
gracious guidance.
It took you long enough.
How silly of you.
Her Majesty is just like any mother.
You're relieved of your confinement.
So I can come pay my morning respects
from now on?
Court Lady Kim.
Tell Officer Seo to bring that girl.
Which girl, Your Majesty?
Court Lady
Hong-si.
How about we tell her she was cast out?
What if she asks
the female officials to find her?
It will complicate things.
I'll go and take her to the palace.
No.
This is urgent, so I'll come with you.
Your Highness.
It seems she's not in the annex.
Where did she go?
Dae-chu, could you go
and check at the Hyeminseo?
Yes, Your Highness.
The Young Master won't be home until 8:00.
Are you sure
you can stay here till that late?
It's all right. Everyone's out.
I have something to talk about
with the Young Master.
Hello?
This voice...
What are you doing here?
May I ask who you are?
Right.
I'm Dae-il's friend from the academy.
I see.
The Young Master is out at the moment.
Well...
I think he's here to see me.
Why did you come here?
Eun-jo.
He's the Young Master's friend.
Mind your tone.
It's fine.
We're past formalities, in every sense.
What?
You're startling her.
I have some business at the Hyeminseo,
so we talk sometimes.
I see.
So? What is it?
Sir?
Someone's looking for Hong-si.
Who's Hong-si?
Court Lady Hong-si?
Yes, that's why I came all the way here.
That should tell you
who's looking for you.
I'm afraid I must go.
All right.
I'll cook the broody hen another time.
Wait.
Eun-jo, wait here.
You should take these.
Why is Mother looking for me?
How would I know?
And why are you making my mother
cook the broody hen?
Mother insisted.
What was I supposed to do?
Could you please not call her "Mother"
like that?
Why did you leave these beautiful things
in your drawer?
They were stored carefully.
No.
Wait.
Is this...
All right.
I did that? I kept them carefully?
Mother...
I mean...
Your daughter must've left them
for a reason.
You didn't need to bring them out.
Pardon?
I'm glad you did.
Give them to me. I'll put them on.
My! Whoever picked out these shoes
has excellent taste.
What about this lotus leaf?
It was next to them.
You even dried this and kept it?
I could tell they were precious to you,
so I kept them.
You can tell, right?
They look
quite precious, even to you, Mother.
No, they're not.
It just came with the silk shoes.
Why are you yelling like that?
Look, you startled my mother.
Apologize now.
I apologize.
It's all right.
What's wrong with you?
I'll leave the lotus leaf here.
It seems too precious.
Why don't you go on ahead?
Mother,
can we have a moment?
Did you want to say something to me?
I know we just met
and this could sound baffling,
but I think you should keep some distance
from your daughter for now.
Because she's married now?
What?
Yes, exactly.
Her husband's family won't be happy
to see her visiting you so often.
You're right.
I was being selfish.
I didn't realize it when she was here,
but now that she's gone,
I miss her so badly.
Same here.
Pardon?
I mean, that's what
your daughter would think.
Anyway,
I will follow your advice
and try to keep some distance.
It won't be too long.
Just for a bit.
I apologize.
I was reminded of my mother.
I see.
And don't cook the precious broody hen
for your daughter.
Give them back. They're mine.
What's mine is yours,
and what's yours is mine.
It's you and me.
Look here,
what does that mean?
That's just how it is now.
What's mine is yours,
and what's yours is mine.
Ever since our bodies were switched,
I feel like I'm on a scavenger hunt.
One by one, I'm uncovering
the things this body's owner hid.
What's next?
Nothing.
About the silk shoes...
I just didn't want to waste them.
I can totally believe that.
I'm heading to my quarters now.
You can go to the courtyard by yourself.
Lower your head.
- Blast.
- Your Highness.
Chief Secretary Im. It's been a while.
Have you been in good health?
I heard about your father's passing.
I sincerely hope that his body,
long wearied by illness,
has now found rest.
Have you ever met my father,
Your Highness?
I heard that he had been gravely ill.
I appreciate
Your Highness' gracious words.
I heard that you visited
His Majesty's bedchamber last night
and cautioned him against
the overuse of medicine, Your Highness.
Yes, I did.
As the Vice Superintendent
of the Royal Pharmacy,
- I'll question the royal physicians--
- Don't.
It's not that serious.
Why press them
when we could just exchange opinions?
As you command, Your Highness.
Good.
I must get going.
You there, Grand Prince's court lady.
Halt.
His Highness dropped this. Take it.
Give it to me.
How dare she...
You there,
did you not hear us?
Court Lady Kim, go to Her Majesty at once.
She sent for you urgently.
Yes, sir.
Let's go to your residence.
Yes.
The Grand Prince doesn't seem
to know much about the incense.
Chief Secretary Im.
Can you tell me the name
of that herb from the Ming?
May I ask the reason
for Your Highness's inquiry?
It would be useful to know,
for my studies.
I might want to use it later too.
It is the seed of a flower called Gokdu,
a medicinal herb found only in the Ming.
Gokdu?
Thank you.
I heard that Your Majesty had sent for me.
Because I wanted to commend you
for your recent service as well.
That you added "as well"
probably means
there's something more important.
I'm impressed.
You're not only agile,
but also quick-witted.
From now on,
observe the Grand Prince closely.
Observe?
I am indeed the most suitable person
for that task.
And look more discreetly
into matters concerning women.
His Majesty's women.
I will look into that matter closely,
as Your majesty commands.
This recent incident worries me.
I worry he may be roaming the market,
associating with some girl
of no name or standing.
Your Majesty,
regarding you said just now...
such worries should never be voiced
in His Highness' presence.
What?
You're right.
He always tends to do
the opposite of what I say.
If I tell him not to do something,
he'll do it even more.
You sure know the Grand Prince well.
There's one more thing.
Find out which woman
was holding his hand in the yard.
If I told Brother about this,
he would fault me for my rashness.
I beg Your Majesty's help.
I dreaded the idea that we would be
tied to the Chief Secretary's family,
so this is for the best.
I will speak to him of it in due time.
I appreciate it.
Hae-rim, are you certain
about this decision?
Rumors of a broken engagement
are harsh on women.
They will cling to you for a while.
I will bear it.
What's taking him so long?
Your Highness, Hong-si is here.
Let her in now.
What did Her Majesty say?
Later. I'm tired.
You didn't make any mistake, did you?
You have no idea
how tiring it is to get around
in this small body.
It's my body. I know that very well.
Stop being a crybaby and get up.
Did he fall asleep?
He must've been really tired.
Let me
keep this.
Stay there.
I didn't know I had such a handsome face.
I'm appreciating it.
At this moment at least,
it doesn't seem all that bad
our souls were switched.
About last night...
I didn't mean it
when I said I would catch you.
No.
I actually wish you meant it.
I did what I did
because
I followed my heart.
I just couldn't stand by and watch
patients who were so malnourished
that even medicine no longer worked.
I know it's hard to understand
why I'm doing this.
Even I don't understand it myself.
"What's wrong with me?
Why am I like this?"
I kept thinking about it,
but I couldn't find the answer.
So I concluded
that this nosiness
is something I was born with.
I concluded that must be it.
Once I no longer needed a reason,
I felt at ease.
It wasn't for anyone else,
but for my own peace of mind.
Selfish, right?
Perhaps,
it's my vanity.
It's your heart.
And your sincerity.
About what you promised the other day...
From now on,
stay within my expectations.
Just stay within
what I can handle.
"But if you go beyond my forbearance
and threaten the foundations of Joseon,
I will arrest you."
That day should never come.
No way.
A petty thief stealing trifles,
could never threaten
the very foundations of Joseon.
Let me promise one thing too.
If I were ever to be caught,
it would be by you.
Your Highness, Officer Seo is here.
Let him in.
The seats.
Should I have read the room
and waited before entering?
Yes. From now on,
count to ten before you enter.
What did Chief Secretary Im mean earlier?
Did you go to His Majesty's bedchamber?
Right.
I forgot to tell you about it
when I met you a couple of days ago.
Do you think the Grand Prince
was sounding you out, Father?
To me, it didn't seem like that.
It didn't to me either.
Then what is bothering you?
Grand Prince Dowol...
That name bothers me.
You made him stop the medicine?
So that's why
the Chief Secretary and Lady Jang
mentioned my name the other day.
His Majesty wasn't upset about it,
so I thought it ended well.
That's my life.
People will find meaning in even
the most meaningless things you say.
Living as a Grand Prince
isn't easy after all.
Simply folding the bedding
can cause an uproar,
and asking for the name of an herb
can lead to the royal physicians
being questioned.
The Grand Prince
can't speak or act freely.
Right.
I forgot that you were now
living as a young widow.
Well,
your in-laws are actually nicer
than I thought.
Really?
That's strange.
I'm living a decent life
as the lady of the annex.
Don't worry about me.
By the way,
His Majesty must've been baffled
to see his brother show such concern.
What's the name
of that medicinal herb again?
They said it's Gokdu.
Is His Majesty getting old?
It seems like his illness
is getting serious.
Are you feeling unwell?
My body has been feeling heavy lately.
I wonder why.
There's been nothing
out of the ordinary lately.
Except that you haven't burned the incense
these past few days.
The incense...
bring it.
His Majesty is showing
strong symptoms of addiction.
If the Grand Prince visited him,
he would not stand by and do nothing.
Ever since the ledger
was handed to His Majesty,
the Grand Prince keeps getting in the way.
Should I have him quietly removed?
If things go wrong...
If things go awry, we will be wiped out.
Pretext.
We need a pretext.
We must scour
the Grand Prince's every move.
Everything, down to the smallest rumors.
Yes, Father.
That was not an order given to you.
This will pressure the Grand Prince.
Keep out of harm's way.
Then, who will do it?
I was posted to State Tribunal
instead of Office of Inspector General.
I heard the Chief Secretary
pulled some strings.
Office of Inspector General?
Was it to scrutinize the corruption
of high officials there?
Or did you wish
to seize the nobles of this country
and stand above them?
Perhaps that's what I should have done.
You do not have the right
to do that.
Because I have never given it to you.
Do not waste words on an animal.
State its use.
What do you think it is?
State Tribunal.
The royal court?
Is that it?
Take everything to the State Tribunal.
Yes, sir!
What are you doing?
Tell me what this investigation is about.
Then, I will submit the report
accordingly.
You don't need to know.
It's confidential.
Wrap it up by 4:00.
Yes, sir.
Gil-dong?
Interesting.
What's that procession over there?
Gil-dong has died.
People have been coming
to offer their condolences
for over ten days now.
Place it there.
This is real money.
The beggars will take it.
Let them.
Gil-dong would've shared
what he'd received with the starving.
A memorial?
It's taking place in the market.
Shouldn't you go?
A memorial?
Gil-dong does not deserve
something like that.
I mean no disrespect to the dead,
but I hope his great name and the rumors
will be buried with him.
DEAD
CATCH GIL-DONG
We both serve the State Tribunal,
but you're a secretary,
and I'm an inspector.
It's because your father
is the current Chief Secretary
and mine's the former Director
of the Office of Royal Decree.
That's not what it is.
I placed first in the exam,
and you got that position
through family connection.
Why do we keep going in circles here?
I want to see what the Grand Prince
of this country looks like
before I go and fetch him.
But he's been in his bedchamber for days.
Now I want to see him more.
Go and see him.
You can just do it.
Apparently, a secretary
of the State Tribunal is not permitted
a free audience with the Grand Prince.
He hasn't been going to the constabulary
these last few days?
His Highness started reading
Four Books and Five Classics again.
Four...
He has not opened a single book
since he was ten.
Could he be ill?
It's not that he didn't read books,
he just pretended...
I wonder if he only pretended
that he didn't read, which is absurd.
I shall look into his condition.
Does she look like her?
What are you doing here?
Her Majesty the Queen Consort
is expected to arrive by noon.
Until then, please remain here
and converse among yourselves.
Yes, ma'am.
It's been so long since we last met.
It's lovely to see you all.
Yes.
Right.
Let us offer comfort to Lady Shin.
Her engagement is soon to be broken off.
I told you it was a secret.
In times of misfortune,
we must comfort one another.
Oh, dear.
What happened?
You must be deeply upset.
I'm fine.
So, tell us.
Why was it broken off?
That's...
If you can't explain yourself
in a situation like this,
all the blame will fall on you.
People will say that you had another man,
that you're unattractive
or that your skin was flawed.
Am I right?
His Highness, Grand Prince Dowol, arrives!
He's the Grand Prince?
An engagement is a promise,
not a vow that must never be broken.
Just because a promise is broken
does not mean there is wrongdoing.
Pardon me
for interrupting your conversation.
It was too irritating to simply pass by.
It has been a while, Your Highness.
Do you know me?
We met the other day
at Her Majesty's residence.
Well...
I don't remember.
I apologize.
Not at all.
Lady Hae-rim of the Shin family?
Yes, Your Highness?
If it would not trouble you,
may I ask for a moment of your time?
Were you addressing me?
That was a classic folk-tale moment.
Prince Charming coming to the rescue
when the heroine is in danger.
Pardon?
So this is how it feels.
I think I'm a natural.
Maybe I should rescue more people.
Pardon.
I guess you don't read folk tales much.
No, I love them.
The Tale of Seodong,
Princess Pyeonggang,
The Pheasant, The Tale of Sukhyang,
Yi Chunpung, Kim Sangseo...
The Tale of Kim Sangseo?
That's a really rare book.
When Seolbing parted ways
with the man she was pledged to for life,
I cried my eyes out.
When Seolbing was reborn
and returned to his house,
I screamed in joy.
But the true charm of this book is that...
Seolbing leads a war to victory
disguised as a man!
You're an avid reader.
- You really enjoyed the book.
- Yes.
Are you really the Grand Prince?
Apparently, with this face.
Surprising, isn't it?
I didn't know Your Highness
was the Grand Prince.
I apologize.
Don't worry.
I was just passing by.
You seemed to be in trouble,
so I wanted to help you.
Did I overstep?
No.
Your Highness stepped in
at the right moment, to the right degree.
Actually, I wanted to apologize to you.
I stained your name,
though I did not mean to.
Will you not ask what it was?
I'm sure you will tell me
when the right time comes.
I appreciate your understanding.
I will tell you everything in due time.
Let go of me.
I said, let go!
Look who's here.
Blast.
We meet again.
Are you acquainted
with Master Jae-i as well, Your Highness?
Well...
I...
Your Highness?
Now I get why you're here
dressed like that.
It's a misunderstanding.
You're a secretary of junior fourth rank.
How dare you stand before the Grand Prince
and not pay your respects?
Shut your mouth.
If I weren't wearing this face,
you'd be dead now.
What is...
I am Jae-i of the Im family,
a secretary of the State Tribunal.
I pay my respects, Your Highness.
Soon,
we shall meet again.
I must be on my way.
I must keep my family under control.
You, follow me.
Stay here.
Don't make it worse.
Your Highness,
is that man next to Hong-si...
You proved yourself useful.
Your Highness,
Hong-si must have arrived
at the Chief Secretary's residence by now.
Things will get more complicated
if I intervene.
It's better that I stay out of it.
Stay out of it?
I'm sure Hong-si will understand,
but it'll hurt her feelings.
It will.
She will certainly be beaten.
Given that temper of his,
he could do something even worse.
They will break all her limbs,
perhaps more.
It seems your feelings have changed.
Are you the same man
who chased Hong-si's carriage
on her wedding day?
I did?
Did you forget?
Because of the rain,
in case Hong-si's carriage tipped over,
at every turn of the road
the bridal carriage would pass,
you had dry sand, straw
and gravel laid out.
That's no different
from chasing the carriage.
You were deeply concerned
about how upset she would be
if her silk shoes got wet.
Seriously, what is wrong
with your lord?
You were so worried
that the bridal carriage
might sway or tip over.
Give me a break.
What am I to do now?
Are you going to Hong-si?
Dae-chu,
bring a horse from the Royal Stables.
From here, go in on your own.
I've been wondering something
the whole way.
Why are you so angry, Grandchild?
What?
I hate to say this again,
but you're acting
like this woman's husband.
Did you forget? It's to keep my family--
I know.
But it sounds like an excuse to me.
When you look at me,
I see turmoil in your eyes.
What are you trying to do?
I'm trying to say nothing should be done.
This is a warning.
Sir.
The Chief Secretary
orders you to come at once.
Go.
It seems like your father
needs you urgently.
That wretch's gaze towards me
is thick with desire.
Has he been harboring those feelings
all this time?
Whatever it is,
he'd better not try anything with me.
Eun-jo.
Your Young Master was waiting for you
for quite some time.
Is that so?
What is this?
They seem like soldiers
from the State Tribunal.
What's this about? Make way.
We meet again,
Your Highness.
He could have waited a little longer.
He didn't even have a little patience.
I'm so tired.
Who are you?
Are you Gil-dong?
As of this moment,
Your Highness is under arrest
for freeing the murderer Gil-dong.
What's happening?
I'm back.
I'm finally back...
Does this mean
Hong Eun-jo is now...
Who are you...
Dae-chu, the sword.
Your Highness!
There has never been such a thing
as a royal siding with thieves!
You look like you're about to confess.
I should've unmasked him
and checked his face first.
Then, I would've been able to protect you
without all this trouble.
Why are you so twisted?
I was just worried...
Don't make me care
about this damned family.
Hong Eun-jo is a married woman.
It seems you don't quite understand
the situation.
So it must be turned back.
Subtitle translation by Sunyoung Baek